ILR School Miscellaneous Publications of the School /3072 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Miscellaneous Publications of the School
1946-2018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3072 PUBS
2.78 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
Training pamphlets, ILR publications, workshop and union information
3081328
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 25, 2019
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 26, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3059: ILR School Press Releases /3060: ILR School Foreign Visitor Information /3061: ILR School Reprints of Articles about the School /3062: ILR School Public Information Center Publications /3063: ILR School Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) Forum /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /3066: ILR School Alumni News /3069: ILR School Scrapbook /3070 mf(d): ILR School Publication "For Our Information" (F.O.I.) Digital from Microfilm /3071: ILR School Albany Extension Division Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
3081328
- Work-Experience Training Programs in Educational and Corrective Institutions by G.E. McGrew, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Abstracts - v.1, no. 1, April 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Labor College (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Publications by ILR (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ILR Publications (Box 1, Folder 5)
- An Analysis of Five Collective-Bargaining Contracts in the Canning Industry of New York State, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Project Manager's Report Sumerbank Executive Training Program, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ILR Publications (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Closing of a Ford Motor Company Plant in Mahwah, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dynamics of Organizational Behavior - Scully, Kesiah E. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Revolving Sex Discrimination Grievances on Campus; Four Perspectives - Farley, Jennie (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Participation in Union Affairs - Davie, Diane J. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- WEBS: A Career and Educational Counseling Service - Wittenberg, Carol (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Work and Environment Initiative Newsletter, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- School of Industrial and Labor Relations Admissions (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- ILR Alumni News, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Union Leadership Institute Tenth Anniversary, 2001-2010 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- I&LR Commentator, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Labor Management Documentation Center (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Scope and Contents
  Leaflet
- International at ILR, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Goals and Resources, ILR Extension, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Skills for More Effective Union Work/New York State Nurses Association, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Uniting a Divided Local Union / Cornell Labor Summer School, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Celebrate 60!, 1947-2007 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Habits and Skills of Successful Union Representatives - Oct. 11, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Union Leadership Institute - Tenth Anniversary, 2001-2010 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Employment, Workplace Practices and Labor-Management Relations in Western New York (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Agreement between Cornell University, ILR Extension, Metropolitan District Office, NYC and the Communication Workers of America, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ILR Extension Credit Programs: Policies & Procedures Manual (Box 3, Folder 9)
- ILR School Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 10)
- ILR School Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lenz Library Resource Lists (Box 3, Folder 12)
- ILR Workshop and Labor Program Information (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Expert Directory, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Stop The Merger, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 15)